Criminal Justice, School of; Records ua640
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Dean's Historical Day Files, 1963 April-1971 June; 1; 0.50 cubic ft.
  - Day Files, 1969 September-1970 January; 1.10
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, 11/01/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 470)
      re minutes of the faculty meeting (retreat of 1969), October 18-19, 1969.
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of faculty, 11/01/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 471)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re emergency faculty meeting, 11/07/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 472)
    - Memo to Alfred P. Finklestein, Chrmn Faculty Senate Executive Committee from Donald J.Newman, Senator, CJ, re Exclusion of the West End Podium Extension, 11/10/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 473)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of faculty meeting 11/3/1969, 11/10/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 474)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda 11/17/1969, 11/12/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 475)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of the emergency faculty meeting, 11/10/1969, 11/13/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 476)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of the faculty meeting 17 Nov. 1969, 11/25/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 477)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda 12/1/1969, 11/25/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 478)
    - Memo to faculty from D. Newman, re spring schedule, Masters Degree Program, 11/25/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 479)
    - Memo to R. Myren from V. O'Leary, re Second Track M.A. Degree, 12/01/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 480)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re Two-Track M.A., 12/05/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 481)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of the faculty meeting on 12/1/1969, 12/12/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 482)
    - Memo to faculty and students from A. Pasciuto, re parking situation, 12/12/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 483)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 12/15/1969 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 484)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting 1/9/1970, 01/07/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 485)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of the faculty meeting on 12/15/1969, 01/09/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 486)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting, 01/23/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 487)
  - Day Files, 1970 February-1970 September; 1.11
    - Memo to faculty from V. O'Leary, re Curriculum Revisions, 02/03/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 488)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, with News and Notes for Feb. 1970, 02/05/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 489)
    - Memo to faculty and students of SCJ from Curriculum and Educational Policy Committee, re Dissertation Prospectus Statement and Examination, 02/11/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 490)
    - Memo to R. Myren from M. O'Neill, 02/11/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 491)
      re procedure used for changing requirements.
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda 2/16/1970, 02/12/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 492)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Russell N. Fairbanks, 02/12/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 493)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of the 2/16/1970 faculty meeting, 02/16/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 494)
    - Governance of the School of Criminal Justice: A Proposal for Change, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 495)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, 03/20/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 496)
      re faculty meeting agenda 4/13/1970.
    - Memo to faculty and students from R. Myren, re Guidelines on Faculty-Student Consultation, 03/30/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 497)
    - News and Notes, SCJ, 1970 April (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 498)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re Postponement of general faculty meeting, 04/07/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 499)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 5/11/1970, 05/04/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 500)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, 05/04/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 501)
    - Letter to Allan A. Kuusisto, President, SUNYA, re Kent State, 05/07/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 502)
    - Letter to Richard M. Nixon from SCJ faculty and students, re slayings at Kent State, 05/08/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 503)
    - Memo to faculty, re minutes of the 20 April 1970 faculty meeting, 05/11/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 504)
    - Resolution adopted by students of SCJ on Michigan State University, School of Criminal Justice, College of Social Science, 05/18/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 505)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, 05/20/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 506)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 5/25/1970, 05/21/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 507)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of 10 May 1970 faculty meeting, 05/22/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 508)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Allan A. Kuusisto, 06/03/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 509)
    - The 126th Annual Commencement State University of New York at Albany, 06/07/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 510)
    - Letter to Dr. Allan A. Kuusisto from E. Lumbard, re three year term on Visiting Committee, 06/11/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 511)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Allan A. Kuusisto, 06/15/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 512)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re Visiting Committee, 06/18/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 513)
    - News and Notes, SCJ, 08/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 514)
    - Memo to faculty from R. Myren, re faculty meeting agenda, 9/1/1970, 08/26/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 515)
    - Rules and Procedures in the Renewal of Faculty Appointments, Continuing Appointments, and Promotions in Rank: School of Criminal Justice, 09/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 516)
    - Operating Policies, SCJ, Academic Year 1970-1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 517)
    - SCJ Faculty, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 518)
    - SCJ Handbook, Fall Semester 1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 519)
    - Memo to faculty from A. Pasciuto, re minutes of 25 May 1970 faculty meeting, 09/08/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 520)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Russell N. Fairbanks, 09/08/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 521)
    - News and Notes, SCJ, SUNYA, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 522)
  - Day Files, 1970 October-1971 June; 1.12
    - Letter to Morton Kamerman from E. Lumbard, 10/02/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 523)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, 10/08/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 524)
    - Memo to the Higher Education Community from Clarence M. Coster, U.S. Department of Justice, re general information - Law Enforcement Education Program (LEEP), 10/09/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 525)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, 10/15/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 526)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, 10/23/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 527)
    - Press Release from Governor Rockefeller's Office, 10/30/1970 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 528)
    - News and Notes, SCJ, SUNYA, 1970 November (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 529)
    - Memo to students from Laud Humphreys, Chairman, Educational Policies Commission, re frustration of proposed changes in requirements for the M.A. and interim measures adopted by the faculty, 01/15/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 530)
    - Grading of Graduate Courses, SUNYA Grad. Off, 01/15/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 531)
    - Policy concerning use of the computer terminal by external faculty and students, adopted by faculty on, 01/18/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 532)
    - SCJ News and Notes, 1971 February (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 533)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, 02/18/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 534)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, 02/23/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 535)
    - SUNYA, SCJ By-Laws, 03/09/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 536)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from William E. Kirwan, 03/23/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 537)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Orrell A. York, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 538)
    - Press Release from Governor's Office, 04/17/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 539)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from William E. Kirwan, Superintendent, NYS Police, re visit to, Undated (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 540)
    - Academy and Division Headquarters, 04/20/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 541)
    - SCJ, SUNYA, Agenda Visiting Committee, 04/23/1971-04/24/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 542)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re Criminal Law Bulletin, 04/28/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 543)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from R. Myren, re Visiting Committee meeting and NSF award, 05/03/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 544)
    - Letter to R. Myren from E. Lumbard, 05/11/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 545)
    - Letter to Dr. Henry Riecken from Earl G. Droessler, 05/18/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 546)
    - Letter to E. Lumbard from Mark Cunniff, 05/21/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 547)
    - Letter to Hon. Irving Lang from E. Lumbard, 05/25/1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 548)
    - Excerpts from 1970-71 Departmental Workload Analysis, 06/1971? (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 549)
    - Dean's Report, SCJ, SUNYA, 1970-1971 (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 550)
    - A SHORT HISTORY OF THE ALBANY GRADUATE PROGRAM IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION, 1971 Fall (Box 1 (1-Dean's Historical Day Files), Folder 551)
- Dean's General Subject Files, 1962-1989; 2; 4 cubic ft.
  Contains general items that pertain to the School of Criminal Justice. Includes general correspondence with faculty, program and course descriptions, draft proposals, grant proposals, press releases, faculty meeting minutes, general planning documents and Dean's Reports. The bulk of the materials falls within the years 1965-1984. The files of Dean Newman, 1977-1984, also contain correspondence relating to accreditation site visits he made to other institutions offering courses in Criminal Justice. Included in Newman's files is correspondence with famed criminologist Marvin E. Wolfgang (1961-1983) and the former Dean of the School of Criminal Justice and School President Vincent O'Leary (1976-1977). In a few cases Newman's files contain the correspondence of O'Leary and Richard Myren. In a number of cases Newman carried on professional correspondences with colleagues both before and after his term as Dean. See the Donald Newman Papers for that correspondence. The bulk of the material dates between 1968 and 1983.
  Arranged Alphabetically.
  - Alumni Survey Questionnaire, 1985 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Applications for admission to graduate and undergraduate study in Criminal Justice, 1983 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - "Archival Material" re formation of the School of Criminal Justice, compiled by R.A. Myren, 1962-1966 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Committee on Institutional Funds, allocated proposals, 1969-1971 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Concept Paper: Development of a Graduate Curriculum in Planning, Research Analysis and Evaluation in Criminal Justice, 1978 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Confessions, Interrogation and the "Right to Remain Silent", ca. 1985 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 1 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1975-1986 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Faculty, 1972 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - Courses, School Bulletins, 1973-1984 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Criminal Justice Film Group, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Dean's Reports, 1967-68 - 1973-74 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - Dean's Reports, 1974-1975 - 1977-1978 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Dean's Reports, 1980-1981 - 1981-1982 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Drafts of Chapters in Progress (Miscellaneous Writings), Undated (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Draft Proposal - Comprehensive program of the fund for the improvement of post-secondary Education of the Department of Health Education and Welfare, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Draft Proposal - Criminal Law Revision, 1966-1967 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Draft Proposal - Establishment of a Law School at SUNYA, 1967 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Draft Proposal - Faculty Development through an Academic Criminal Justice Information Dissemination Service, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Faculty, SCJ, 1968 October-1971 December (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Faculty/Graduate Student Profiles - School of Criminal Justice, 1988 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Faculty Recruiting, Undated (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 17)
  - Handbook/Guide for Teaching Assistants, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 18)
  - Hindelang Criminal Justice Research Center, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 19)
  - History, SCJ, 1976 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 20)
  - Internal Review of M.A. and Ph.D. Programs, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 21)
  - Long Range Planning, March, 1966-November 1967 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 22)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 23)
  - Paralegal Program, 1974 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 24)
  - Pinkerton Visiting Professor, 1972-1975; 1977 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 25)
  - Placement - May 1972 M.A. Graduates (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 26)
  - Police Science Programs - Universities, Colleges, Junior Colleges in the U.S., Undated (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 27)
  - Press Releases, 1967-1973 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 28)
  - Qualifying Student Examination - Student Answers, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 29)
  - Recruitment Correspondence, 1967-1968; 1971-1972 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 30)
  - Space Planning, 1968 January-1968 October (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 31)
  - Supplement to the SUNYA Faculty Handbook for the SCJ, 1975-1976 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 32)
  - Status Report, 1973 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 33)
  - Three Year Plan, 1978-1979 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 34)
  - Undergraduate Program Advisement Manual, 1985-1986 (Box 2 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 35)
  - Dean Donald Newman, 1977-1984 (rec); 2.45
    - Acker, James R., 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Administrative Interest Group, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Alaska, University of, Evaluation, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - American University, Evaluation, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Austin, Dr. W. Timothy, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Chicago, University of Illinois at, Evaluation, 1984 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Citizens Crime Commission of N.Y.C., Inc. (Eliot Lumbard), 1978 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Clarke, R.V.G., 1981-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - Cohen, Fred, 1978-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - Cutshall, Charles, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - Dean's Council Meetings, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 11-12)
    - Duffee, David, 1978-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Elliston, Fred, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Engle, Donald, 1977-1979 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Faculty Committees, 1979-1980; 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 16-17)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1977-1978; 1978-1979; 1979-1980; 1980-1981; 4 folders (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 18-21)
    - Faculty Recruitment Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 22)
    - Faculty Salaries, 1971-1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 23)
    - Faculty Workload, 1981 April (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 24)
    - Farnworth, Margaret, 1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 25)
    - Farrell, Ron, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 26)
    - Felkenes, George - Michigan State University, 1977-1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 27)
    - Flanagan, Tim, 1982-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 28)
    - Florida International University, Evaluation, 1977 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 29)
    - Foley, Denis - Post-Doctoral Fellow, 1977-1979 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 30)
    - Foster, Price, 1977-1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 31)
    - Fox, James W., 1976-1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 32)
    - Georges, Daniel, 1977-1979 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 33)
    - Goldkamp, John - Temple University, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 34)
    - Gottfredson, Don, 1976-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 35)
    - Gottfredson, Michael, 1979-1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 36)
    - Hardt, Robert, 1961-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 37)
    - Hindelang, Michael J., 1970-1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 38)
    - Hindelang, Michael J. - Memorial Scholarship Fund, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 39)
    - Hirschi, Travis, 1976-1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 40)
    - Ilchman, Warren, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 41)
    - In-Hak Yoo, 1980-1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 42)
    - Kenefick, Donald P., 1979-1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 43)
    - Kirk, Stuart A., 1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 44)
    - Kress, Jack, 1973-1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 45)
    - Landau, Shima, 1977-1978 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 46)
    - Lejins, Peter, 1977-1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 47)
    - Levine, Howard, 1979-1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 48)
    - Lofton, Colin, 1979-1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 49)
    - Lumbard Award, 1981-1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 50)
    - Lumbard, Eliot H., 1978-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 51)
    - MacDonald, Donald G., 1977-1978 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 52)
    - Malinchak, Alan A., 1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 53)
    - Manning, Peter K., 1981-1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 54)
    - Massachusetts Department of Youth Services, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 55)
    - McAnany, Patrick, 1978 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 56)
    - McCleary. Richard, 1981-1983 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 57)
    - McConville, S.D.M., 1981-1982 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 58)
    - McNulty, John - Albany County Sheriff, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 59)
    - Merit Increases, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 60)
    - Minnesota, University of, Evaluation, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 62)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 3 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 63)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 1)
    - Morgan, John, 1977-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 2)
    - Morgenbesser, Leonard, 1979-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 3)
    - Munro, Jim, 1974-1980 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 4)
    - Murphy, Patrick V., 1982-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 5)
    - Murphy, Patrick - Commissioner N.Y.P.D., 1970-1971 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 6)
    - Nebraska, University of, Evaluation, 1976 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 7)
    - Newman, Graeme, 1972-1983 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 8)
    - North Carolina Central University, 1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 9)
    - N.Y.C. Police Alumni, 1978 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 10)
    - O'Leary, Vincent - President SUNY Albany, 1968-1977 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 11)
    - Palmer. Ted B., 1980 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 12)
    - Pelfrey, William V., 1981-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 13)
    - Pennsylvania, University of, 1978 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 14)
    - Pierce, Lawrence, W., The Honorable, 1969-1981 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 15)
    - Pochoda, Dan, 1981-1982 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 16)
    - Police Executive Research Forum (P.E.R.F.) - Gary P. Haynes Exec. Dir, 1980 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 17)
    - Pope, Carl, 1975-1988 (Box 4 (2-Dean's General Subject Files), Folder 18)